calloptionputoption.com 2010-04-02

# Privacy_policy

**Privacy policy               ****                                                                                                                                                                                   
****     ****calloptionputoption.com Advisory Services   ("calloptionputoption.com") is committed to safeguarding your privacy  online. Please read the following privacy policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full  use of our many offerings. This policy may change from time to time and hence please check periodically.  
****  
****1\. INFORMATION GATHERED AND/OR                                                                                                                                                           ****  
********calloptionputoption.com gathers two types of data about users.  
(a) personal information that individual users provide through registration as paid subscribers and voluntarily at certain other  points; and   
(b) tracking information, which is automatically collected about every visitor to the website paid subscribers.** **2\. CANCELLING SUBCRIPTIONS                                                                                                                                                                      
********A subscriber is not entitled to cancel his membership, and claim back his subscription. His membership automatically stands   cancelled, once he does not renew his subscription next month.  
********3\. PERSONAL INFORMATION                                                                                                                                                                         ********Personal information is gathered for several ways. First, when a user registers for a paid subscription, he/she is required to   provide his/her name, city of residence, email address and to select a login name.

Although all this information is generally entered into fields on a secured area of the website, subscribers can talk offline to  our customer service representative and receive a computerised invoice by mail.

Wherever we collect personal information, we make an effort to include a link to our Privacy Policy on that page.

** **  
****4\. USE OF THE INFORMATION                                                                                                                                                                         
********calloptionputoption.com uses information obtained from its users to enhance their experience on the website.

We do not rent or sell any personal information about our subscribers or other users. As a general rule, we will not disclose  any personal information to any third parties, except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or if the subscriber  has given permission, for example by voluntarily entering a contest, where the information is required to register for the  particular contest is provided to the partner operating the contest.

calloptionputoption.com may disclose account or personal information in special cases when we have reason to believe that  disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating  calloptionputoption.com's Terms of Service or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally )  calloptionputoption.com rights or property, other calloptionputoption.com users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.  calloptionputoption.com may disclose or access account or personal information when we believe in good faith that the law  requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products  and services.

** **  
****5\. CORRECTING THE INFORMATION                                                                                                                                                               ********The accuracy of your personal information is important to us. If you are a paid subscriber and have a concern about your   personal or account information maintained at calloptionputoption.com, or want to correct, update, or confirm your information,  please send us an email at Customer Service Desk. We will be happy to review and update your information with our records.

If you identify any error in your personal information or need to make a change, please contact us by email and it will be  promptly attended to.

** **** **6\. SECURITY PRECAUTIONS TO PROTECT THE LOSS, MISUSE, ALTERATION OF INFORMATION                                                                  
********:Your subscriber account information and your profile are password-protected so that you and only you have access to this   personal information. You may correct your personal information as explained in Section 5.

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. calloptionputoption.com will never ask you for your password in  an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window  when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information if you share a  computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or an Internet cafe.

Because the nature of the Service provided on calloptionputoption.com, has users all over the world, and takes adequate steps to  ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with the relevant Terms of Service and this Privacy Policy.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a  result, while we strive to protect your personal information, calloptionputoption.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any  information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to  ensure its security on our systems.

** **** **7\. WHAT ELSE SHOULD I KNOW ABOUT PRIVACY?                                                                                                                                        
********Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online. In short, if you post personal   information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account or personal  information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

****           **

**Trade In Call and Put Option**

**Home  ||  [NSE](http://www.nseindia.com/)  || [ BSE](http://bseindia.com/)  ||  [SEBI](http://www.sebi.gov.in/)  ||  Contact Us  ||  Disclaimer  ||  Privacy Policy  ||  Subscribe Us  ||  Help

Copyright © 2008 calloptionputoption.com  All rights reserved. 

****Rights of Subscription Reserved.** **  
**This site can be best viewed in IE 5.0 or above, 1024 x 768 Resolution.
